dbbsrv.com 2003-04-01

# Dark Blue Affiliate System: Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY

The Internet, Privacy, and Darkblue.com (DARKBLUE)

The Internet contains a wealth of information; unfortunately, it may also contain personal details about you that you don't want everyone to know. For example, your real name (lots of people on the Internet use aliases, alter egos or nicknames), street address, phone number, or e-mail address. When you go online, sites you visit may be gathering information about you without your knowledge. At Darkblue.com we strive to help our customers protect their privacy while using our services.

Darkblue.com's Privacy Policy

Darkblue.com's policy is to respect and protect the privacy of our users. This policy statement tells you how we collect information from you and how we use it. Using the Internet should be a fun experience and we want to help you make it so.

The information you provide for your personal Darkblue.com account is shared among the Darkblue.com sites, as it is our goal to make your visits to our sites easy and enjoyable. However, be assured that Darkblue.com will not disclose your personal information to third parties without your consent. Darkblue.com may disclose user information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Darkblue.com's rights or property, other Darkblue.com users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Darkblue.com may disclose user information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.

Darkblue.com shares aggregate information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors and other third parties. For example, we will say Darkblue.com's audience is x percent females and y percent males. This data is used to customize Darkblue.com’s content and advertising to deliver a better experience for our users.

There are cases where Darkblue.com may ask you for personal information such as your name, email address, and birth date. For example, we request personal information when you register for a Darkblue.com email account, for transactions, or for services that require registration or subscription. Darkblue.com needs to collect this information for fulfilling prizes, tracking/verifying compliance with Darkblue.com policies as well as federal, state and local laws and/or for editorial and feedback solicitation purposes.

In case you change your mind or some personal information may change (such as your zip code), we will endeavour to provide a way to correct, update or remove the personal data you give us. You can do this at the member information page or by contacting our Customer Support organization at customercare@Darkblue.com.

Opting-Out

Information provided at the time of Registration or submission from a guest may be used for marketing and promotional purposes by Darkblue.com and our affiliates or companies that have been pre-screened by Darkblue.com. To keep you in control of your personal information and the communications directed to you, we allow you to opt-out of the following services: sharing your information in our member directory, receiving communications from Darkblue.com about new features or services, and receiving communications about offers from third-party companies that offer a product or service that we think would be of value to you. If a guest objects to such use for any reason, he/she may stop that use -- either by e-mail request to customercare@Darkblue.com or by modifying his/her member information online.

Use of IP Address

An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Web. Web servers -- the big computers that "serve up" Web pages -- automatically identify your computer by its IP address.

Darkblue.com collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to report aggregate information to our advertisers, and to audit the use of our site. When guests request pages from Darkblue.com sites, our servers log the guests' IP addresses. We do not normally link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that a user's session will be logged, but the user remains anonymous to us. We can and will use IP addresses to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our house rules or terms of service or to protect our service, site, customers or others.

Some services within Darkblue.com, such as certain message boards, may display IP addresses along with the message poster's name and message. Please review each service prior to use and only uses those that disclose information you are comfortable with sharing.

Use of Cookies

What are cookies? Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make Web-surfing easier for you by saving your preferences while you're at our site. We never save passwords or credit card information in cookies. The use of cookies is an industry standard -- you'll find them at most major Web sites.

By showing how and when guests use a site, cookies help us see which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the site are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies. We use the information from cookies to provide services better tailored to our users needs.

Darkblue.com has two primary uses for its cookies. First, we use them to specify unique preferences. For example, in Darkblue.com's Business Centre, users can specify listings across several news topics. This way you don't have to tell us over and over again about the kinds of news stories you want to see. Secondly, we use cookies to track user trends and patterns. This helps us better understand and improve areas of the Darkblue.com service that our users find valuable. While both of these activities depend on the use of a "cookie," visitors to Darkblue.com always have the option of disabling cookies via their browser preferences. Information from cookies is sometimes attached to messages sent to our Customer Service department.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, note that some parts of the Darkblue.com service will not function properly or may be considerably slower if you refuse cookies. For example, without cookies, you will not be able to set personalized news preferences or you may have difficulty completing shopping transactions, entering contests, or playing games.

You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers. Darkblue.com does not control these cookies. The use of advertising cookies sent by third-party servers is standard in the Internet industry.

Links to Other Sites

Users should be aware that when you are on Darkblue.com, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other sites from Darkblue.com pages that take you outside our service. For example, if you "click" on a banner advertisement or an Darkblue.com category listing, the "click" takes you off the Darkblue.com site. This includes links from advertisers, Center sponsors, affiliates and partners that may use Darkblue.com's logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other sites may send their own cookies to users collect data or solicit personal information.

Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online --- for example, via message boards or chat --- that information can be collected and used by people you don't know. While Darkblue.com strives to protect its user's personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk.

Darkblue.com's policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond Darkblue.com's control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation.

Your Acceptance of These Terms

By using this site, you signify your assent to the Darkblue.com Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our sites. Your continued use of the Darkblue.com sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.
